[
    {
        "front": "うつす",
        "back": "映す \nto reflect",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいが",
        "back": "映画 \nmovie",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいがかん",
        "back": "映画館 \nmovie theatre",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "えいが",
        "back": "映画 \nmovie",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "けいかく",
        "back": "計画 \nplan",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほんが",
        "back": "日本画 \nJapanese painting",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おと",
        "back": "音 \nsound",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おんせい",
        "back": "音声 \nsound",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "はつおん",
        "back": "発音 \npronunciation",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうおん",
        "back": "高音 \nhigh tonal pitch",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "たのしい",
        "back": "楽しい \nenjoyable",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "おんがく",
        "back": "音楽 \nmusic",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "らくな",
        "back": "楽な \neasy, comfortable, relax",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "うた",
        "back": "歌 \nsong",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "かしゅ",
        "back": "歌手 \nsinger",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "うたう",
        "back": "歌う \nto sing",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "うつす",
        "back": "写す \nto copy",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃしん",
        "back": "写真 \nphotograph",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "まっくろ",
        "back": "しゃしん \npitch black",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "まんなか",
        "back": "真ん中 \ncentre",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "まっしろ",
        "back": "真っ白 \npure white",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "しんじつ",
        "back": "真実 \ntrust, truth",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "たび",
        "back": "旅 \ntrip",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょこう",
        "back": "旅行 \ntravel",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょかん",
        "back": "旅館 \njapanese style inn",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "よのなか",
        "back": "世の中 \nworld, society",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "せかい",
        "back": "世界 \nworld",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "せわ",
        "back": "世話 \nto care",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいき",
        "back": "世紀 \ncentury (21st century)",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "せかい",
        "back": "世界 \nworld",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいかい",
        "back": "政界 \npolitical world",
        "chapter": "N4 K5"
    }
]